<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<jobs>
<job>
  <partnerJobId><![CDATA[REC- 316-20251219-090432]]></partnerJobId>
  <title><![CDATA[Community Planning Support Officer]]></title>
  <company><![CDATA[City of Karratha]]></company>
  <location><![CDATA[Karratha, Western Australia, Australia]]></location>
  <description><![CDATA[<p>Are you an organised and detail-oriented professional with a passion for supporting community infrastructure projects? The City of Karratha is seeking a Community Planning Support Officer to join our dedicated team and help deliver impactful projects that enhance our community’s future.</p>

<p><b>About the Role</b></p>
<p>This position will assist the Community Planning Team throughout the entire community infrastructure project lifecycle, from inception to final design brief handover, ensuring adherence to contemporary project management practices.</p>

<p>The Community Planning Support Officer will be responsible for supporting procurement processes, administration tasks, and activities that contribute to the planning and execution of community infrastructure projects.</p>

<p><b>Key Responsibilities:</b></p>
<ul>
<li>Assist in the coordination, management, and planning of community infrastructure projects.</li>
<li>Support senior staff with planning, investigation, feasibility studies, and design activities to ensure successful community infrastructure project delivery.</li>
<li>Actively participate in the development of the Community Planning Team, contributing to the creation of effective policies and procedures.</li>
<li>Provide administrative support, including scheduling meetings, preparing agendas and minutes, handling correspondence, records management and following up on outstanding issues, as needed.</li></ul>

<p><b>Why Join Us?</b></p>
<p>At the City of Karratha, we pride ourselves on fostering a positive and dynamic work environment where your contributions make a real impact. Here’s what you can look forward to:</p>
<ul>
<li>A collaborative and supportive team culture.</li>
<li>The opportunity to work on meaningful projects that benefit the community.</li>
<li>Competitive salary and benefits package.</li>
<li>Professional development and career growth opportunities.</li></ul>

<p><b>What We’re Looking For</b></p>
<ul>
<li>Previous experience in a similar role within a dynamic organisation</li>
<li>Previous experience in technical construction and contract administration is desirable</li></ul>

<p>If you’re eager to contribute to meaningful community projects and work in a dynamic environment, we want to hear from you! Apply today and be part of a team that’s shaping the future of the City of Karratha.</p>]]></description>
  <applyUrl><![CDATA[https://karratha.t1cloud.com/T1Default/CiAnywhere/Web/KARRATHA/Public/Function/%24ORG.REC.EXAPN.WIZ/RECRUIT_EXT?suite=CES&token=90a6ad69-5793-4426-ad29-f786540a4db6]]></applyUrl>
  <jobtype><![CDATA[FULL_TIME]]></jobtype>
  <expiryDate><![CDATA[01/09/2026]]></expiryDate>
  <workplaceTypes><![CDATA[On-site]]></workplaceTypes>
</job>
</jobs>
