<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<jobs>
<job>
  <partnerJobId><![CDATA[REC-336-20251208-133501]]></partnerJobId>
  <title><![CDATA[Senior Strategic Planner]]></title>
  <company><![CDATA[City of Karratha]]></company>
  <location><![CDATA[Karratha, Western Australia, Australia]]></location>
  <description><![CDATA[<p>Are you ready to shape the future of civil construction and maintenance in one of the most dynamic and fast-growing regions? The City of Karratha is seeking a motivated and skilled Operations Projects Officer to drive the planning, development and delivery of critical infrastructure and renewal projects that keep our city moving. </p>
<p>If you thrive in a fast-paced environment, love solving complex challenges, and enjoy working across a variety of civil projects from concept through to completion — this is your opportunity to make a genuine impact. </p>
<p><b>About the Role</b> </p>
<p>As our Operations Projects Officer, you will take the lead on capital works and renewal programs — ensuring projects are well-planned, well-managed and delivered to high contemporary standards. You’ll help shape new project management processes, champion innovation within the Operations team, and work closely with engineers, contractors, consultants and stakeholders across the City. </p>
<p>Every day is different. From feasibility studies and tender coordination to stakeholder engagement, budgeting, long-term planning and contract administration — you’ll be at the centre of delivering infrastructure that supports our community now and into the future. </p>
<p><b>What You’ll Bring</b> </p>
<p>We’re looking for someone who is proactive, organised and passionate about delivering outstanding project outcomes. </p>
<p><b>You will have:</b> </p>
<p>Tertiary qualifications in Project Management, Engineering or a related field<br/>Experience in civil construction, engineering or a project management environment<br/>Strong project administration and contract management skills<br/>A solid understanding of infrastructure practices, procurement and Australian Standards<br/>Excellent communication, negotiation and stakeholder-management abilities<br/>Confidence working autonomously while contributing positively to a collaborative team<br/>Strong budgeting, reporting and analytical skills<br/>A commitment to safety, quality and continuous improvement .</p>
<p><b>Why Join Us?</b> </p>
<p>At the City of Karratha, you’ll be part of a dedicated team that values innovation, collaboration and high-quality service delivery. You’ll have the opportunity to work on diverse and meaningful projects that create lasting benefits for our community — and see the real impact of your work every day. </p>]]></description>
  <applyUrl><![CDATA[https://karratha.t1cloud.com/T1Default/CiAnywhere/Web/KARRATHA/RedirectToFunction?token=7561913d-d59e-4e73-8277-05806fbb469c&f=%24ORG.REC.MYAPN.WIZ&suite=CES]]></applyUrl>
  <jobtype><![CDATA[FULL_TIME]]></jobtype>
  <expiryDate><![CDATA[12/22/2025]]></expiryDate>
  <workplaceTypes><![CDATA[On-site]]></workplaceTypes>
  <salaries>
    <salary>
      <highEnd>
        <amount><![CDATA[122525]]></amount>
        <currencyCode><![CDATA[AUD]]></currencyCode>
      </highEnd>
      <period><![CDATA[YEARLY]]></period>
    </salary>
  </salaries>
</job>
<job>
  <partnerJobId><![CDATA[REC-331-20251208-134432]]></partnerJobId>
  <title><![CDATA[Road and Footpath Sweeper]]></title>
  <company><![CDATA[City of Karratha]]></company>
  <location><![CDATA[Karratha, Western Australia, Australia]]></location>
  <description><![CDATA[<p>The City of Karratha is offering an opportunity for an experienced and suitably qualified Accountant to join our Financial Services Team.</p>
<p>This position is based in Karratha, offering an attractive salary and a range of other benefits including, but not limited to:</p>
<ul>
<li>Allowances</li>
<li>Six weeks’ annual leave</li>
<li>13% Superannuation</li></ul>
<p>As a member of the financial services team the Assistant Management Accountant is responsible for assisting with the Annual Budget, Budget Reviews, and Long term financial plans as required.</p>
<p>The role also supports the Management Accountant in preparing the Council’s annual budget and budget reviews, responds to audit enquiries, and oversees the accounts receivable, invoicing, and debt recovery processes.</p>
<p>Qualifications and experience required for the role:</p>
<ul>
<li>A relevant tertiary qualification in finance/ accounting</li>
<li>A minimum of 2 years’ experience in a similar position within a medium to large organisation</li>
<li>A current C Class drivers licence</li>
<li>A National (or Federal) Police Certificate (no more than 6 months old)</li></ul>
<p><b>Why Join Us?</b></p>
<ul>
<li>Competitive salary and benefits.</li>
<li>A supportive and inclusive work environment.</li>
<li>Opportunities for professional growth and development.</li>
<li>Play an important role in the City’s financial future.</li></ul>]]></description>
  <applyUrl><![CDATA[https://karratha.t1cloud.com/T1Default/CiAnywhere/Web/KARRATHA/RedirectToFunction?token=5f3e0559-093c-4ae9-9c21-863a729ec82f&f=%24ORG.REC.MYAPN.WIZ&suite=CES]]></applyUrl>
  <jobtype><![CDATA[FULL_TIME]]></jobtype>
  <expiryDate><![CDATA[12/22/2025]]></expiryDate>
  <workplaceTypes><![CDATA[On-site]]></workplaceTypes>
  <salaries>
    <salary>
      <highEnd>
        <amount><![CDATA[50]]></amount>
        <currencyCode><![CDATA[AUD]]></currencyCode>
      </highEnd>
      <period><![CDATA[HOURLY]]></period>
    </salary>
  </salaries>
</job>
</jobs>
